Jinyeong Seo

Email: jinyeong.seo@snu.ac.kr Homepage: https://jin-yeong-seo.github.io/

Overview

I am a graduate student at Seoul National University, advised by Prof. Yongsoo Song. My research interest lies in (but is not limited to) the practical instantiation of cryptographic protocols using techniques from lattice-based cryptography. Specifically, my recent research focuses on improving the performance of lattice-based proof systems and homomorphic encryption schemes. I also have broad interests in the theoretical foundations of cryptographic proofs.

Education

Seoul National University

Seoul, South Korea

Ph.D. in Computer Science Mar. 2022 – Present

Advisor: Prof. Yongsoo Song

KAIST

Daejeon, South Korea

B.S. in Mathematical Science Mar. 2016 – Aug. 2021

(double major: computer science)

Publications

Authors are listed in alphabetical order by last name, unless an asterisk(*) is indicated.

Conferences

[C07] Simpler and faster BFV Bootstrapping for Arbitrary Plaintext Modulus from CKKS

Jaehyung Kim, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song *ACM CCS 2024*.

[C06] Concretely Efficient Lattice-based Polynomial Commitment from Standard Assumptions

Intak Hwang, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *CRYPTO 2024*.

[C05] Optimizing HE operations via Level-aware Key-switching Framework

Intak Hwang, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *WAHC 2023.*

[C04] Asymptotically faster multi-key homomorphic encryption from homomorphic gadget decomposition

Taechan Kim, Hyesun Kwak, Dongwon Lee, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *ACM CCS 2023.*

[C03] Toward Practical Lattice-based Proof of Knowledge from Hint-MLWE

Duhyeong Kim, Dongwon Lee, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *CRYPTO 2023*.

[C02] Accelerating HE Operations from Key Decomposition Technique Miran Kim, Dongwon Lee, Jinyeong Seo, Yongsoo Song. *CRYPTO 2023*.

[C01] Faster TFHE Bootstrapping with Block Binary Keys

Changmin Lee, Seonhong Min, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *ACM ASIACCS 2023.*

Journals

[J01] *HEaaN-STAT: a privacy-preserving statistical analysis toolkit for large-scale numerical, ordinal, and categorical data

Younho Lee, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yujin Nam, Jiseok Chae, Jung Hee Cheon *IEEE TDSC 2023*.

Experiences

CryptoLab Inc.

Seoul, South Korea

- Researcher Sep. 2019 – Mar. 2020 - Intern Jun. 2019 – Aug. 2019

- Developed HEaaN-STAT, homomorphic encryption-based statistical analysis toolkit.

eWBM Inc.

Seoul, South Korea

- Intern Jun. 2018 – Aug. 2018

- Developed ECDH PKI protocols for secure communication on LoRa devices.

Talks

Practical Lattice-based Private Stream Aggregation and Application to Federated Learning Aug. 2023

The 5th Privacy-Preserving Machine Learning Workshop 2023

Awards

Korea Cryptography Contest

Oct. 2023

Top Award (\$10, 000) National Security Research Institute

29th Samsung Humantech Paper Award

Feb. 2023

Silver Award (\$7, 000) Samsung Electronics

Korea Cryptography Contest

Oct. 2022

Excellence Award (\$2,000) National Security Research Institute

GitHub Repositories

https://github.com/SNUCP/level-aware-ksw PoC Implementation of [C05]
https://github.com/SNUCP/snu-mghe PoC Implementation of [C04]
https://github.com/SNUCP/fast-ksw PoC Implementation of [C02]
https://github.com/SNUCP/blockkey-tfhe PoC Implementation of [C01]

Skills **Programming** : C, C++, Go, Python